eplsite.com 2010-03-29

# 

Privacy Policy If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at . vikkurtiharika9985@gmail.com. At eplsite.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by eplsite.com and how it is used. Log FilesLike most standard Web site servers, eplsite.com use log files. This includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, internet service provider ( ISP ), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Cookies and Web Beacons eplsite.com does not use cookies. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and third party ads. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on eplsite.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. eplsite.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. eplsite.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' Last Updated 26 Aug 2009
